<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experience on The Artful Dev</title>
    <link>https://blog.yurukov.org/categories/experience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Experience on The Artful Dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 15:30:37 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.yurukov.org/categories/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Rainy Sunday</title>
      <link>https://blog.yurukov.org/posts/a-rainy-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 15:30:37 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.yurukov.org/posts/a-rainy-sunday/</guid>
      <description>Today is Sunday. It is raining.
Piano
Yesterday I jumped out of a plane, 3500 meters high, at 240 km/h. The wind just blows everything off you! There is nothing like it!
As you are so far above the clouds&amp;hellip; you think differently. Because of the &amp;ldquo;lighter&amp;rdquo; air, your brain gets less oxygen and you start feeling dizzy, almost drunk.
And what are you doing with your life? I played some piano, had a good, healthy breakfast, learned some Chinese through a favourite song of mine, learned what a tremolo on the piano is and how to play it, got some afternoon sleep in the calming, soothing wind and rain outside, and am about to embark on an adventure to go and see my grandma, because she is waiting for me and she is alone these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initial blog program</title>
      <link>https://blog.yurukov.org/posts/initial-blog-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 10:44:37 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.yurukov.org/posts/initial-blog-program/</guid>
      <description>Dear reader,
I hope you find yourself reading these lines. I hope you feel your connection with me and with yourself.
This morning whilst planning this text and drinking my cup of water on my balcony I saw on the opposite balcony a boy, a neighbor, painting the railings on his terrace. He had well-defined muscles, although they were not something extraordinary. He was beautiful. In one hand he was holding his painting brush somehow clumsily and it was as if he was obliged to paint.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>